[
    {
        "question": "Where is the world-famous Skytree tower located?",
        "answer": "Tokyo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which South American city is laid out in the shape of a puma?",
        "answer": "Cusco, Peru"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after Marco Polo?",
        "answer": "Venice"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after Lester Pearson?",
        "answer": "Toronto"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after Toussaint Louverture?",
        "answer": "Port-au-Prince"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after Ted Stevens?",
        "answer": "Anchorage"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after Galileo Galilei?",
        "answer": "Pisa"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what mountain range is Mount Ansel Adams?",
        "answer": "The Sierra Nevada"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Gaza Strip extends northeast from what peninsula?",
        "answer": "Sinai Peninsula"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Brenner Pass lies on the border of Austria and what other country?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Before being renamed, what was Mumbai called?",
        "answer": "Bombay"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to a city called Truth or Consequences?",
        "answer": "New Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official state animal of Wisconsin?",
        "answer": "Badger"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the 760-foot volcanic crater located near Honolulu, Hawaii?",
        "answer": "Diamond Head"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many US states border West Virginia?",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river flows through the city of Baghdad?",
        "answer": "Tigris"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mountain chain extends from western Canada down through Northern California?",
        "answer": "The Cascades"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mt. Blanc is the highest peak in what mountain range?",
        "answer": "The Alps"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Venezuela?",
        "answer": "Caracas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Caracas is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Venezuela"
    },
    {
        "question": "Caracas is the capital of which South American country?",
        "answer": "Venezuela"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city is the capital of the Austrian state of Tyrol?",
        "answer": "Innsbruck"
    },
    {
        "question": "Innsbruck is the capital of which Austrian state?",
        "answer": "Tyrol"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tyrol is a state located in which European country?",
        "answer": "Austria"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Greece?",
        "answer": "Athens"
    },
    {
        "question": "The remains of which ancient city are found in Iraq?",
        "answer": "Babylon"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you most likely encounter a Tasmanian devil?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Spain?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which tribes are native to New Zealand?",
        "answer": "Maori"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country is the Great Sandy Desert located?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state is closest to Bermuda?",
        "answer": "North Carolina"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country of Europe is called the land of humane bullfights: where the bulls are not killed?",
        "answer": "Portugal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is over 90% of the world`s fresh water supply located?",
        "answer": "Antarctica"
    },
    {
        "question": "What colors are the Swiss Flag?",
        "answer": "Red and White"
    },
    {
        "question": "On Homeland Security`s Color-Coded Advisory System, what does the color blue mean?",
        "answer": "Guarded, second from the bottom"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest point in the United States?",
        "answer": "Denali (formerly Mt. McKinley)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Volleyball Hall of Fame located?",
        "answer": "Holyoke, Massachusetts"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that shares a land border with Haiti?",
        "answer": "The Dominican Republic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that shares a land border with Vatican City?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that shares a land border with Portugal?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that shares a land border with Denmark?",
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that shares a land border with Qatar?",
        "answer": "Saudi Arabia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tirana is the capital of which European country?",
        "answer": "Albania"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Krung Thep is more commonly known as?",
        "answer": "Bangkok"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the nickname for Reading, Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Pretzel City"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which large bay would you find the Belcher Islands?",
        "answer": "Hudson Bay"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Colorado?",
        "answer": "Denver"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Djibouti?",
        "answer": "Djibouti City"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Pettit National Ice Center located?",
        "answer": "Milwaukee, Wisconsin"
    },
    {
        "question": "By what name was Milwaukee`s Pettit National Ice Center known as until 1991?",
        "answer": "Wisconsin Olympic Ice Rink"
    }
]